=Love Start From Marriage= =Episode 11=
= الحب يبدأ من الزواج = = الحلقة 11 =
This is our new design director,
هذا هو مدير التصميم الجديد لدينا ،
Xia Qianxun.
شيا تشيان شون.
Welcome.
أهلا وسهلا.
We'll be working together.
سنعمل معًا.
I would appreciate your guidance.
سأكون ممتنا لتوجيهاتك.
(How can I stay low key with the title of boss lady?)
(كيف يمكنني البقاء هادئًا مع لقب سيدة الرئيس؟)
Sula,
سولا ،
why don't we go and talk to her?
لماذا لا نذهب ونتحدث معها؟
With all the gossips, you can nearly flop.
مع كل الثرثرة ، يمكنك التقليب تقريبًا.
Who are you bitching?
من أنت الشقاوي؟
Mr. Gu.
السيد.  قو.
Why did you hire Xia Qiange?
لماذا قمت بتعيين (شيا تشيانج)؟
She's Xia Qianxun, the wife of CEO Gu.
إنها Xia Qianxun ، زوجة الرئيس التنفيذي Gu.
Notice,
يلاحظ،
knock before you come in.
طرق قبل أن تدخل.
Mr. Gu...
السيد.  قو ...
Don't ever make a fuss about Xia Qianxun's identity.
لا تثير ضجة حول هوية Xia Qianxun.
You're off from work for the next few days.
أنت خارج العمل خلال الأيام القليلة القادمة.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Like I said,
كما قلت،
put away your sneaky ideas that shouldn't be.
تخلص من أفكارك الخادعة التي لا ينبغي أن تكون.
Since you struggle to do that,
بما أنك تكافح من أجل القيام بذلك ،
I'm lending you a hand.
أنا أمدك يد المساعدة.
I am a hit of the Gu's.
أنا ضرب من Gu's.
Upset as you are,
منزعج مثلك ،
there's no need to suspend me.
ليست هناك حاجة لتعليقي.
Your popularity comes from the Gu's capital.
شعبيتك تأتي من عاصمة Gu.
Anyone can replace you.
يمكن لأي شخص أن يحل محلك.
Mr. Gu, that's not what I meant...
السيد جو ، هذا ليس ما قصدته ...
Get out.
اخرج.
Before I call the security.
قبل أن أتصل بالأمن.
Jin Sula,
جين سولا ،
right?
الصحيح؟
Is there any beef between you and me?
هل بيني وبينك لحم بقر؟
Why do you keep targeting me?
لماذا تستمر في استهدافي؟
Xia Qiange, you know better.
شيا تشيانج ، أنت تعرف أفضل.
Dear.
عزيزي.
Could you make me a cup of coffee?
هل يمكنك صنع فنجان قهوة لي؟
(How is it possible for Mr. Gu to make coffee for someone?)
(كيف يمكن للسيد جو أن يصنع القهوة لشخص ما؟)
Here.
هنا.
I don't like this flavor.
لا أحب هذه النكهة.
What would you like to drink then?
ماذا تريد ان تشرب بعد ذلك؟
Let's buy it together.
دعونا نشتريه معًا.
Qiange.
Qiange.
Haven't seen you for a while.
لم أراك منذ فترة.
You're prettier.
انت اجمل.
You're talking to the wrong person.
أنت تتحدث إلى الشخص الخطأ.
Come on.
هيا.
After all these years with you,
بعد كل هذه السنوات معك ،
you think I can't recognize you?
هل تعتقد أنني لا أستطيع التعرف عليك؟
I am the wife of Gu Chengze, Xia Qianxun.
أنا زوجة Gu Chengze ، Xia Qianxun.
There's a special scar on that private area of yours.
هناك ندبة خاصة في تلك المنطقة الخاصة بك.
I suppose Gu Chengze doesn't know it, huh?
أفترض أن Gu Chengze لا يعرف ذلك ، أليس كذلك؟
Qiange.
Qiange.
How could you just marry a random guy
كيف يمكنك الزواج من رجل عشوائي
just because I broke up with you?
فقط لأنني انفصلت عنك؟
Stop being a smart ass.
توقف عن كونك حمارًا ذكيًا.
Get straight to the point.
توجه مباشرة إلى الهدف.
I've been working on a program.
كنت أعمل على برنامج.
But there's a lack of fund.
لكن هناك نقص في التمويل.
Now that you're the boss lady of the Gu's,
الآن بعد أن أصبحت سيدة Gu's ،
I suppose a borrowing of two-hundred thousand won't be too much.
أفترض أن اقتراض مائتي ألف لن يكون كثيرًا.
Why don't you just go robbing?
لماذا لا تذهب فقط للسرقة؟
I think you have my back.
أعتقد أن لديك ظهري.
Moreover, we had something beautiful.
علاوة على ذلك ، كان لدينا شيء جميل.
For old time's sake,
من أجل الزمن القديم ،
lend me a hand.
تقديم يد المساعدة.
One hundred thousand at most. No bargain.
مائة ألف على الأكثر.  ليست صفقة.
Deal.
صفقة.
Don't ever talk about my identity.
لا تتحدث أبدًا عن هويتي.
Trust me.
صدقني.
One more thing.
شيء اخر.
Keep Susu near yourself.
حافظ على سوسو بالقرب من نفسك.
Do not let her appear in my sight.
لا تدعها تظهر في عيني.
Qiange.
Qiange.
I know you've always had me in your heart.
أعلم أنك كنت دائمًا ما كنت في قلبك.
Hit the road.
انطلق الى الطريق.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You are...
أنت...
Hi, Mr. Gu.
مرحبا سيد.  قو.
My name is Li Zhuo.
اسمي لي تشو.
I'm Xia Qian...
أنا شيا تشيان ...
I'm classmates with Xia Qianxun in college.
أنا زملاء الدراسة مع Xia Qianxun في الكلية.
Welcome to suggest.
مرحبا بكم في اقتراح.
(He's the ex-boyfriend of Xia Qiange,)
(إنه الصديق السابق لـ Xia Qiange ،)
(Li Zhuo.)
(لي تشو.)
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
You can't be blinded by anger and marry Mr. Gu
لا يمكنك أن يعمي الغضب وتتزوج السيد قو
because of me and Li Zhuo.
بسببي ولي تشو.
(What's his purpose of talking to Qianxun?)
(ما هو هدفه من التحدث إلى Qianxun؟)